<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fairytale Stories Book</string>
    <string name="background_image">Background Image</string>
    <string name="settings_icon">Settings Icon</string>

    <string name="cinderella_story_text">Once upon a time, there was a beautiful girl named Cinderella who lived with her cruel stepmother and stepsisters. They treated her very poorly, making her do all the chores and never allowing her to rest.\n\nOne day, an invitation arrived at their home. It was for a grand ball at the palace, where the prince would choose his bride. Cinderella\'s stepmother and stepsisters were overjoyed, but they forbade her from attending.\n\nAs Cinderella watched them prepare for the ball, she couldn\'t help but feel sad. Suddenly, her fairy godmother appeared and transformed her rags into a beautiful gown, a pumpkin into a carriage, and mice into horses. She warned Cinderella to return home before midnight when the magic would wear off.\n\nCinderella arrived at the palace and captivated everyone with her beauty. The prince was immediately drawn to her, and they danced the night away. But as the clock struck midnight, Cinderella remembered her fairy godmother\'s warning and fled, leaving behind her glass slipper.\n\nDetermined to find the mysterious maiden, the prince searched the kingdom, asking every maiden to try on the glass slipper. When he arrived at Cinderella\'s house, her stepsisters tried to squeeze their feet into the slipper, but it didn\'t fit.\n\nFinally, Cinderella tried on the slipper, and it fit perfectly. Overjoyed, the prince realized she was the one he had been searching for. They were married, and Cinderella forgave her stepmother and stepsisters, inviting them to live with her in the palace.\n\nAnd so, Cinderella lived happily ever after, proving that kindness and goodness always triumph in the end.</string>
    <string name="snow_white_story_text">Once upon a time, in the middle of winter, when snowflakes were falling like feathers from the sky, a queen sat sewing at her window, which had a frame of black ebony wood. As she sewed, she pricked her finger with the needle, and three drops of blood fell on the snow. The red looked so beautiful on the white snow that she thought, "If only I had a child as white as snow, as red as blood, and as black as the wood of the window frame." Soon after, she had a daughter who was as white as snow, with lips as red as blood, and hair as black as ebony. She was named Snow White. Sadly, the queen died after giving birth to her. A year later, the king married another woman who was beautiful, but proud and cruel. She could not bear that anyone should surpass her in beauty. She had a magical mirror, and she would ask it: "Mirror, mirror, on the wall, who in this land is fairest of all?" The mirror would answer, "You, my queen, are fairest of all." But as Snow White grew up, she became more and more beautiful. When she was seven years old, she was as beautiful as the clear day and even more beautiful than the queen herself. When the queen asked her mirror: "Mirror, mirror, on the wall, who in this land is fairest of all?" It answered, "You, my queen, are fair; it is true. But Snow White is a thousand times fairer than you." The queen was shocked and became yellow and green with envy. From that moment on, whenever she saw Snow White, her heart turned over inside her, so great was her hatred for the girl. She ordered a huntsman to take Snow White into the woods and kill her. But the huntsman took pity on her and let her go. After the huntsman spared Snow White, she fled into the dark forest and found refuge with seven dwarfs. Meanwhile, the jealous queen, disguised as an old hag, tricked Snow White into eating a poisoned apple. Snow White fell into a deep sleep, waiting for true loves kiss to awaken her.</string>
    <string name="sleeping_beauty_story_text">
Once upon a time, there lived a king and queen who had a daughter named Aurora. To celebrate her birth, they invited all the fairies to bestow blessings upon her. However, they forgot to invite one wicked fairy who cursed Aurora to prick her finger on a spinning wheel and die. Luckily, a good fairy softened the curse, stating that Aurora would instead fall into a deep sleep, to be awakened by true loves kiss.To protect Aurora, the king ordered all spinning wheels in the kingdom to be destroyed. However, on her sixteenth birthday, Aurora encountered an old woman spinning in a tower. Ignorant of the curse, she pricked her finger and fell into a deep slumber.

The good fairy put the entire kingdom to sleep until Aurora could be awakened.

Many years passed until a prince, drawn by the legend of the sleeping princess, braved the thorns and awoke Aurora with a gentle kiss.

The kingdom rejoiced, and Aurora and the prince lived happily ever after.
</string>
    <string name="beauty_beast_story_text">In a quaint village, a merchant named Maurice lived with his three daughters, Beauty being the youngest. The family lost their wealth, and Maurice stumbled upon the Beasts castle. He plucked a rose for Beauty, angering the Beast, who demanded Maurices life in return. Out of love, Beauty offered herself in his place.

At the castle, Beauty encountered the fearsome Beast, but over time, she discovered his kindness and gentleness. Despite her initial fear, Beauty found solace in the Beasts company. Meanwhile, Maurice returned home, and Beautys sisters plotted to improve their fortunes by marrying wealthy suitors.

As Beauty spent more time with the Beast, she began to care for him deeply. One day, she dreamt of her father falling ill and begged the Beast to let her visit him. The Beast agreed, providing her with a magical mirror and ring for her safe return.

Upon reaching home, Beauty nursed her father back to health but delayed her return to the castle. When she finally returned, she found the Beast lying motionless. Distraught, she confessed her love, and a miracle happened. The Beast transformed into a handsome prince, revealing that true love had broken the curse.

Beauty and the prince were married, and their love brought prosperity to both their families. They lived happily ever after, a testament to the power of love and kindness.</string>

    <string name="little_red_riding_hood_story_text">In a small village, Little Red Riding Hood lived with her mother. One day, her mother asked her to take a basket of goodies to her grandmother who lived in the woods. Little Red Riding Hood set off, promising to stay on the path. On her way, she encountered a cunning wolf who tricked her into revealing her destination. The wolf, with malicious intent, reached her grandmothers house first, pretending to be Little Red Riding Hood. Upon arriving, the wolf devoured the grandmother and lay in wait. When Little Red Riding Hood arrived, she was surprised to see how different her grandmother looked. The wolf, pretending to be her grandmother, urged her to come closer. But just as the wolf was about to pounce, a woodcutter passing by heard Little Red Riding Hoods screams and rushed to her aid. He swiftly killed the wolf and rescued both Little Red Riding Hood and her grandmother. From that day forth, Little Red Riding Hood learned to be cautious and always obey her mothers instructions. The village rejoiced in their safety, and Little Red Riding Hoods adventure became a cautionary tale for all.</string>






</resources>